Previously on Hostages...
前情提要
When are you speaking with the Vice President?
- 你什么时候去见副总统 - 我现在就去
We're going to discuss potential running mates for his presidential campaign.
我们要商量和他一同总统竞选的潜在伙伴
When I'm finished, you will be at the top of his list.
等我完事儿 你会是他名单上的第一个
So you've made up your mind to run when Kincaid's second term is up?
所以你决定在Kincaid第二次任期结束后参选?
The only question is, are you interested in running?
唯一的问题 你有兴趣参选吗
I have a business proposition for you.
我有个生意上的提议给你
I need a spy inside Duncan's operation.
我想要在Duncan的行动里安插一个间谍
What about the girl? She accept your offer?
- 那女孩儿怎么样? 接受你的提议了吗? - 她加入了
The President is gonna be in New York today.
总统今天会在纽约 会召集另一队人马
Sir, I've got a hit on Duncan Carlisle in New York.
长官 我在纽约发现Duncan Carlisle
- 15 minutes ago. - Son of a bitch.
- 15分钟前 - 王八蛋
He's trying to sabotage this whole thing.
他要破坏整个计划
- Targets are down. - Copy that.
- 目标倒地 - 收到
- I can't believe you did it. - You came through for me, Ellen.
- 不敢相信你做到了 - 你为我冒了险 Ellen
Without you,
没有你 我不知道今天会发生什么
Don't move!
不许动
There's easier ways to get in touch with me, Logan.
你要跟我联系 有很多更简单的办法的Logan
Phone call, text, send me an e-mail.
电话 短信 邮件
We know what you did in New York.
我们知道你在纽约干了什么
- People are very upset. - I'm upset too, now what?
- 大家很愤怒 - 我也很愤怒 现在怎样?
Not my call.
这不是我说的算
Agent Carlisle. We've never officially met.
Carlisle特工 我们没有正式见过
Thomas Blair.
Thomas Blair
I'm aware of what you and your team did in New York.
我知道了你和你的手下在纽约的所做所为
And I'm aware of what you and your team tried to do.
我也知道你和你的手下想要做什么
Should've stayed out of it.
你不该插手的
If you had succeeded, that would've made me expendable,
如果你成功了 那样我就可有可无了
- and we both know where that leads. - You're smart.
- 我们都知道接下来会如何 - 你很聪明
I'm also your best chance at getting this thing done.
我依然是你成功的最大希望
We could still work together. You already failed once.
- 我们可以继续合作 - 你已经失败过一次了
Why should I believe you'll succeed this time?
我为什么要相信你这次会成功?
Well, for starters, I just took out your crackerjack sniper team.
首先 我想干掉你出色的狙击手
And you're confident Dr. Sanders will come through for us?
- 你相信Sanders医生会帮我们? - 我确定
And you're confident you'll hold up your end of the bargain?
你也有自信 你会兑现你的承诺?
Dr. Sanders will need a certain amount of help in the operating room.
Sanders医生在手术室需要一定的帮助
- We need to talk about that. - What the hell does that mean?
- 这我们再商量 - 这话什么意思
A problem has come up.
出了一个问题 我们需要你帮忙解决
Right.
是啊
I mean, everything's been so confusing and...
大家都很混乱
heightened.
很激动
I know what I'm supposed to feel. I'm supposed to hate you.
我知道我应该怎么想 我应该恨你的
But, uh...
但是...
I don't.
我不恨
I'm glad to hear that.
这很好
Ellen, we can't. We need to focus right now
Ellen 我们不可以
- saving our families. - Yeah.
- 救我们的家人 - 是
We're doing the right thing.
我们在做对的事
I gotta head out. I just got a call from a detective.
我得出去一下 刚接到一个警探的电话
- About? - The murder of that limo driver.
- 关于? - 轿车司机的谋杀案
One of the detectives working on the case wants to talk to me about Jake's testimony.
负责这案子的一名警探 想跟我谈一下Jake的证词
What number did he call you on?
他打的是你哪个号码?
My work number. Called my secretary and she told me to call here.
我的工作号码 打给了我的秘书 她跟我说回复这个号码
Check it yourself. Press redial.
你自己看 按重拨
Do you really want the DC police knocking on the door, asking where the hell I am?
你真想警局的人来敲门 问我在哪儿?
Archer will give you a ride.
Archer会送你去
Burton, hey.
Burton 嘿
I need you to check something out. Right away!
帮我查点东西 马上
I'd like to talk to Detective Hall.
我想找Hall警探
- Is he expecting you? - No.
- 他知道你来吗 - 不知道
- What's it about? - I'd rather talk to him directly.
- 有什么事 - 我想直接跟他说
He's in court right now, he should be back pretty soon.
他现在在法庭上 应该很快回来
- Okay, I'll wait. - Follow me.
- 好 我等着 - 跟我来
- I thought we had a deal! - We did, we still do.
- 我以为咱们说好了 - 是的 现在也是
I gave you $10,000 as a gesture of good faith and you screwed us.
我给你一万表示对你的信任 结果你耍了我们
I told you I needed to know where Duncan was, if he did anything out of the ordinary.
我说了我需要知道Duncan在哪儿 他是否有异常举动
The man went to New York and took out a team of assassins!
那家伙去了纽约 干掉了一支暗杀队伍
Not only did you fail to warn us, you went completely off line.
你不仅没有提醒我们 还完全联系不上
Listen! Duncan ordered me to shut off my phone.
听着! Duncan让我关掉手机的
Then he had me and another guy parked on a stake-out all day.
然后让我和另一个人在外面埋伏了一整天
If I tried to call you, my cover would've been exposed.
我要是打给你 我就暴露了
You're saying you had no idea what he was up to?
你是说你完全不知道他的计划
No. Not a clue, I swear.
不知道 毫无头绪 我发誓
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
我会再给你一次机会
To save your ass and live happily ever after with your son in Canada.
让你救自己一命 可以跟你儿子开心地在加拿大生活
What do I have to do?
我要怎么做?
When this operation is over, we're going to eliminate a few loose ends.
等这次行动结束 我们要铲除几个后患
- A few? - Three.
- 几个? - 三个
Duncan, Archer and Kramer.
Duncan Archer和Kramer
Assuming you're on board, of course.
前提当然是你和我们一伙 不然的话 就是四个
I'm on board.
我加入
Hey. Your lawyer's here.
嘿 你的律师到了
Hello, Brian.
你好 Brian
What are you doing?
你怎么来了
- I'm here to help. - This is a police station. When that detective comes in here,
- 我是来帮忙的 - 这里是警局 等那个警察走进来
I'm gonna tell him everything! You can't stop me!
我会告诉他一切 你休想阻止我
You're right, but hopefully I can convince you you're making a mistake.
你说得对 但希望我能说服你 这样做是错的
I doubt it.
我表示怀疑
Patty Hearst, she was taken hostage,
Patty Hearst 曾被挟持为人质
locked in a closet,
被锁在一个柜子里
and after months of abuse, her captors robbed a bank.
经过几个月的折磨 挟持她的人打劫了一家银行
Patty Hearst was caught, on tape, helping them.
Patty Hearst被抓 在录像里 协助他们
She was tried for bank robbery, and in spite of the fact that
她被证实参与了银行抢劫 尽管她是被绑架
- Well, this is different. - You're right, it's even worse.
- 这不一样 - 你说得对 这样更糟
You're crazy!
你疯了
Your wife injected the President with blood thinners,
你妻子给总统注射了薄血剂
lied to the Secret Service.
欺骗了特勤处
- Helped bury her friend... - The police are going to believe us!
- 帮忙埋了她的朋友 - 警察会相信我们
Not you.
不是你
- You think so? - I know so.
- 你这么想的? - 我知道会的
Tough to prove you're a victim, when you're kissing the captor.
很难证明你是受害者 因为你吻了绑匪
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 人质 第一季第12集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 人质 第一季第12集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：奶酪站住
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：我要去香港啦 校对：我尽量不哭出来 时间轴：奶酪站住
Congratulations, you've successfully doctored
祝贺 你成功P了一张我妻子和Duncan接吻的照片
No one's gonna think that's real.
没人会以为是真的
There's video, as well.
还有视频的
It's real, Brian.
这是真的 Brian
How's it going? I'm Detective Hall.
- 怎么样? - 我是Hall警探
So, what can I do for you?
有什么可以帮你的?
Well, after, um, consulting with my attorney,
在咨询过我的律师之后
I realize that the information I was about to disclose is inaccurate.
我意识到我想公开的信息并不准确
Excuse me?
什么?
Sorry for the inconvenience. I made a mistake.
抱歉给你添麻烦了 是我搞错了
I have nothing to say.
我没什么可说的
Where have you been? I've just been trying to call you.
你去哪儿了 我一直在打电话给你
You kissed him?
你吻了他?
- What? - I saw the photo, Ellen!
- 什么? - 我看到照片了 Ellen!
Photo? What are you talking about?
照片? 你说什么呢
I went to the DC Police Department, I was gonna tell them what's going on.
我去了华盛顿警局 要告诉他们事情的真相
- What! You were gonna talk to the police? - We need help, Ellen, okay?
- 什么! 你要告诉警察? - 我们需要帮助 Ellen 好吗
There's no other way out of this, so yeah, I went to the police,
没有别的出路 所以是的 我去了警局
and Burton Delaney was there and he showed me a photograph of you and Duncan.
但是Burton Delaney在那儿 给我看了你和Duncan的照片
Kissing.
接吻
Is it real?
是真的吗
Yeah.
是
Yes, we kissed. Once.
是 我们接吻了 一次
God.
天啊
What the hell is wrong with you?
你在想什么啊?
I just, I was trying to convince him that I...
我就是...想说服他 我...
- I was willing to cooperate. - Oh, so, you kissed him?
- 我愿意合作 - 噢 所以就跟他接吻了?
Is that what you're saying?
你是想说这个意思吗?
I'm saying it just happened, okay. I don't know why. It just did.
我是想说事情就那么发生了 好吗 我不知道为什么 就是发生了
I'm sorry, that's the honest truth.
我很抱歉 这是大实话
Look, I understand things just happening, I do,
听着 我明白有些事会自然发生 真的
but not with that son of a bitch!
- 但不是跟那个王八蛋 - 不是你想的那样
What the hell does that mean?
这话是什么意思
He's doing this to save his wife.
他这么做是为了救他妻子
- Where's Sandrine? - She went to see the lawyer about her son.
- Sandrine人呢 - 她去见律师谈她儿子的事了
So, what's up?
怎么了?
- Where you been? - Talking to our partners.
- 你去哪儿了 - 见我们的搭档
They know we took out their hit team. They think, or they know?
- 他们知道是我们干的了 - 他们是以为 还是知道了?
- Know. - How?
- 知道 - 怎么会
Let's just say these guys have lots of resources. Good news is they don't hold a grudge.
只能说他们消息灵通 好在他们并没有怀恨在心
The mission is still a go, but there's one slight hiccup.
行动照旧 但是有一个小麻烦
A Secret Service agent named Jack Cahill,
有一名叫Jack Cahill的特勤处特工
has just been assigned to the President's personal detail, and he's senior to our inside man.
被派为总统的贴身保镖 他是我们线人的上级
Which means, Logan won't have operational control on the day.
也就是说 Logan当天不会指挥行动
Exactly. Unless, we find a way to remove Cahill.
没错 除非 我们想办法弄走Cahill
Not that easy to take out a Secret Service agent.
想干掉特勤处特工不是那么容易的
I didn't say we were gonna kill him. I said, we need to remove him.
我没说要杀了他 我说 得把他弄走
I have a plan.
我有个计划
Who cares why he's doing all this?
管他为什么这么做啊? 重点是他做了
And he's harming innocent people in the process.
并且过程中他在伤害无辜的人
To hell with his damn wife. What makes her so special?
让他的老婆见鬼去吧 她怎么就与众不同了?
- She's dying, he loves her. - That doesn't justify killing someone.
- 她要死了 他爱她 - 那也不代表可以随便杀人
Well, the only person who was supposed to die was Kincaid, that's it.
唯一一个该死的人是Kincaid 就是这样
Ellen, listen to yourself, "The only person who was meant to die?"
Ellen 听你自己在说什么啊 "唯一一个该死的人?"
- Like that's okay? - Kincaid is a bad person...
- 无所谓吗 - Kincaid是个坏人
- Says Duncan. - Well, I believe him.
- Duncan说的 - 我相信他
I met with Nina's mom and she confirmed everything. It's all true.
我见过Nina的母亲 她确认了一切 这都是事实
Okay. Great.
好 好极了
It's true.
是真的
Kincaid's a monster, he's like, the most horrible guy in the world,
Kincaid是个坏人 他是...这世上最可怕的人了
but that doesn't mean that it's okay to kill him.
但那也不代表着可以杀了他
And Duncan's wife being sick doesn't entitle him to commit murder!
Duncan的妻子生病也不意味着他就有权利杀人
Look, you know, I dunno, life isn't fair. Okay?
你瞧 我也不知道 人生就是不公平的 好吗
Good people die, bad people live.
好人不长命 祸害遗千年
There's no rhyme, no reason, no justification, it's just
说不清 倒不明 没有合理解释 就是...
the way it is.
事实就是这样
Well thank you, Colonel.
谢谢 上校
I don't mean to impose, but I was just in for a procurement meeting
我没想打扰的 但我本来要跟 一位联席参谋长开采购会
- No, I'm glad you did, Lyndon. - So, how are things going?
- 不会 我很高兴你来了 Lyndon - 事情进展如何?
You know how it is. Wars are won and lost over the long haul.
你是清楚的 战争到最后总会有输赢
Power is like business.
权力就像生意
Lots of ups and downs, you just wanna make sure it all pays off in the end.
有很多起伏 你只希望到最后一切都有回报
Now, this most recent setback has been a little disturbing.
最近的这次小失败有点令人烦忧
And my company made substantial investments,
我的公司做了大量投资
with the understanding that OTI would continue.
都是在OTI会继续的前提下
It represents government contracts worth billions to us.
这代表跟政府签的合约对我们来说价值数十亿
I have some good news on that front.
我正好有这方面的好消息
The President has decided to wait a few weeks to expose it.
总统决定等几个星期再曝光
That is good news.
这是好消息
Happy to walk you through the game plan, if you'd like?
我很乐于把游戏安排跟你说一下 有兴趣吗
Oh, no. Details make me nervous. I just wanna make sure that
不必了 细节会让我紧张 我只想确保
we are all heading in a direction that is in our mutual best interest.
咱们方向一致 是为了大家共同的利益
Oh, I understand. Have faith. The balance of power is shifting, soon.
我明白 要有信念 权力平衡很快就会改变
Oh, son. The balance of power is always in the same place.
孩子 权力平衡从来不会改变
Where the money is.
都在钱的那一边
- Thanks for meeting me. - Thanks for calling.
- 多谢你见我 - 谢谢你来电
So, like I said on the phone,
正如我在电话里说的
- I got some work for you. - Great.
- 我有工作给你 - 很好
This gig's a little different. It requires discretion.
这个活儿有点不同 需要小心谨慎
Discretion costs extra.
谨慎就要多花钱
Not a problem.
不成问题
What the hell were you thinking, going to the police?
你在想什么啊 去找警察?
- Screw you! - You are minutes away from signing your own death warrant.
- 去你的吧! - 你差一点就给自己签了一张死亡执行书
- Go to hell. - Three more days, that's it, then we're gone.
- 去死吧你 - 再过三天 就三天 我们就结束了
- Out of your lives forever. - I don't believe a word you're saying.
- 永远消失在你们的生活里 - 你说的一个字我都不信
Your wife does.
你妻子相信
- Excuse me? - Your wife. Ellen.
- 你说什么 - 你妻子 Ellen
She believed me.
- 她相信我 - 你少提我妻子
- I hope you burn in hell. - I probably will.
- 我希望你下地狱 - 我应该会的
But, that won't change a damn thing.
但那也改变不了任何事
How did it go with your lawyer?
你跟律师谈得怎么样?
Good. He's trying to work out a custody arrangement.
很好 他在谈抚养权协议
It's not easy though, it's not like I can go to court and talk about my stable career.
不过不容易 我又不能上庭 介绍我的稳定职业
- So, your lawyer, he's based here? - Excuse me?
- 那你的律师 他是在这边工作的? - 什么意思?
Just wondering since your son's in New York, thought you have a New York attorney.
我就是想既然你儿子在纽约 你应该有个纽约的律师
You a family law expert, now?
你现在成家庭法专家了?
Just concerned about you.
我是关心你
You worry too much.
你操心太多了 对心脏可不好
You're right. Need to lighten up a little.
你说得对 应该放松一点
Relax, start doing yoga.
放轻松 做做瑜伽
Drinking chamomile tea.
喝洋甘菊茶
Getting homework done?
做完作业了吗
Some, but, it's kinda hard to have focus on calculus these days.
一部分 不过最近很难专心做微积分
This will all be over soon.
这一切很快就会结束的
Look, um, I need a phone, one that can't be traced or listened to.
我需要一部手机  不会被查到或是监听的
You think you can borrow one, from a friend?
你觉得能跟朋友借一部吗?
Mom said that we need to cooperate,
妈妈说我们需要合作 只要照他们说的做 就什么事儿都不会有的
I know what Mom said.
我知道妈妈说了什么
- But... - Look, I need to make a phone call.
- 但是... - 听着 我需要打个电话
Your mother's doing what she thinks is right and I respect that,
你妈妈在做她认为对的事 我尊重她
but I think I know a way out of this and I just gotta make a phone call.
但我想我有办法逃出去 我只是需要打个电话
Can you help me out?
你能帮我吗
Clear a path! Make way! Hang in there.
让开! 让一让 坚持住
Move, move, move. Excuse me!
让开 让开 借过一下
He can wait.
- 他可以等等 - 这边 神经外科医生在等了
- Hey, I got your page, what have we got? - Multiple gunshot wounds. Chest and legs.
- 我接到呼叫了 什么情况 - 身上多处枪伤 胸部和腿
He's losing a lot of blood. We need to get him on the table.
他失血过多 我们得把他抬到手术台上
Take him to OR four, we'll both scrub in.
带他去四号手术室 我们俩都准备手术
So, what are the specifics?
- 具体细节是什么 - 这些就是
They're shaped charges.
聚能炸药
They're small, powerful, and untraceable.
轻巧 强大 不可查
I need you to attach one to each vehicle.
我要你在每部车上都装一个
What about the detonators?
那引爆装置呢
I'll handle that.
我会搞定的
When the surgery is over, the team is gonna split up and disappear.
等手术结束 所有人解散 消失
That's when the bombs are gonna go off.
到时候炸弹就会引爆
I'll take care of it.
- 我会处理好的 - 今天就处理
I met up with our girl.
我跟那姑娘见过了
- All systems go. - Good.
- 一切就绪 - 很好
But there's something else, D.
但还有件事 D
It's about Sandrine. I think she's playing us.
是关于Sandrine 我觉得她在耍我们
What?
什么?
She was acting suspicious, so, I followed her today.
她的举止很可疑 所以我今天就跟踪了她
Met a guy at the park. Car with government plates.
在公园跟一个人见了面 他开着政府牌照的车
I think she flipped.
我觉得她叛变了
If she flipped, we'd already be in prison.
她要是叛变 我们已经在牢里了
So, she isn't talking to the Feds, who's that guy?
那她如果不是跟联邦的人告密 那人是谁呢
What this guy look like?
这人长什么样子
Like a fed. Tall, fit, white, about 45.
像个FBI 高个子 健美 白人 45左右
- Is this the man she was talking to? - Yeah, that's him.
- 是这个男人吗 - 对 就是他
On the right. Who is he?
右边这个 他是谁
My contact at the Secret Service.
我在特勤处的联络人
Why the hell is she talking to him?
- 她为什么跟他见面啊 - 问得好
Okay, I think I've got the last of the bleeders. How are you doing?
好 我想最后的出血点已经止住了 你怎么样
Still closing holes.
还在缝合
Looks like the bullet missed his major arteries.
看来子弹没有射中他的主动脉
- He just might make it. - Vitals are stabilizing.
- 他或许挺过来了 - 生命迹象都稳定
- Hey, this is an operating room! - Is that son of a bitch gonna live?
- 嘿 这里是手术室 - 那王八蛋会活着吗
- Sir, please step out of the room. - My partner just died.
- 长官 请离开这里 - 我的搭档刚死了
Your patient shot him in the face.
你的病人打中了他的脸
Just keep that in mind while you're trying to save his sorry ass.
在你救他的时候 别忘了这件事
What's going on?
怎么回事?
This guy ambushed two cops, during a traffic stop.
这家伙伏击了两个警察 在停车的时候
The one who got shot was a young father. He just had his first kid.
中枪的那个是新爸爸 第一个孩子刚出生不久
You need to be careful around Sandrine.
在Sandrine身边时多加小心
Come on, Duncan, I'm not a kid.
行了 Duncan 我不是小孩子
I'm not worried about you getting your heart broken.
我不是担心你会伤心
I'm saying you can't trust her.
我是说你不能相信她
- What are you talking about? - She's a criminal.
- 你在说什么啊? - 她是个罪犯
She plays by different rules.
她按照不同的规则做事
- You don't know her. - Neither do you.
- 你不了解她 - 你也不了解
I think she might be selling us out.
我觉得她可能在出卖我们
- To who? - Logan.
- 跟谁 - Logan
I don't buy that. If she's selling us out,
我不信 如果她出卖我们
why'd she take out that sniper team in New York?
- 为什么在纽约干掉狙击手? - 我不知道
In the meantime, I want you to take her with you and watch a guy named Steve Patterson.
与此同时 我要你带她 去监视一个叫Steve Patterson的人
- What are we watching him for? - Nothing.
- 监视什么? - 什么都不用
It's a fake mission, but if she is working for the other side, word will get back to them.
是假任务 但如果她是为另一边做事的 他们就会收到风声
I wanna see if Sandrine takes the bait.
我想知道Sandrine是否会上钩
How you doing?
你好吗?
Fine.
挺好
Why?
怎么了?
Just thought, after what happened in New York, if you wanted to talk about it.
就是想在纽约的事情之后 你或许会想聊一聊
There's nothing to talk about. I did what I had to do.
没什么好聊的 我做了必须做的事
If the two shooters had the drop on me,
如果那两个枪手先瞄准我
they would've put a bullet in my head in a heartbeat.
他们会马上一枪打死我
- That's how it works. - Got it.
- 就是这样 - 明白
Duncan wants us to scope out this address.
Duncan要我们去这个地方监视
Who lives there?
谁住在那儿
Some federal prosecutor. His name is Steve Patterson.
一个联邦检察官 他叫Steve Patterson
I'll get my gear.
我去拿家伙
- We're losing him, what happened? - I've got him all cleaned up here.
我们要失去他了 怎么回事? 我这里都清理好了
I pulled out a bullet fragment that was blocking his femoral vein,
我把卡在他大腿动脉的子弹碎片取了出来
I can't stop the bleeding...
我止不住出血
- Push one cc of epi. - Close the bleeder, Lena.
推1cc肾上腺素 缝合出血点Lena
I'm trying, Ellen. There's too much blood.
我在努力了 Ellen 出血太严重了
I said epi now!
我说马上注射肾上腺素
He's gone, Ellen. There's nothing we can do.
他走了 Ellen 我们无能为力
- Okay, step out of the way. - What are you doing?
- 好吧 让开 - 你干什么?
Expose the patient, I need paddles.
把病人空出来 给我电击板
Clear!
让开
- There's too much damage. - Just give me some space.
- 损伤太严重了 - 给我点空间
Suction, roll of vicryl.
吸入器 多聚管
You did it.
你成功了
I can't believe it!
不敢相信
Close him up.
给他缝合
You ready?
准备好了?
Just throwing my bag in the back.
把我的包扔到后面
Why are we staking out this prosecutor?
我们为什么要盯着这个检察官?
- It have to do with the limo driver? - I don't know.
- 跟轿车司机有关吗? - 我不知道
I gotta be honest, I can't forget that guy's face.
坦白说 我老是忘不掉那家伙的脸
I can't get it out of my mind.
在我脑海里挥之不去
He was pointing a gun at me. You saved my life that night.
- 他用枪指着我 - 那天晚上你救了我的命
Well,
是啊
you'd do the same for me, right?
你一样也会救我的 对吗
Of course.
当然了
Ellen?
Ellen?
I didn't mean to...
我没想...
I thought he was dead.
我以为他死了
I certainly wasn't trying to kill him.
我肯定不是想杀了他
Well, you weren't trying to save him either.
你也不是想救他
Look, my hand aren't as good as yours. I didn't think we could save him.
你瞧 我没有你那么厉害 我不认为我们能救活他
Not to mention, the son of a bitch is gonna die anyway.
更不用说 那王八蛋早晚都会死
He's a cop killer, Ellen. He's gonna get the death penalty...
他杀了警察 Ellen 他会被判死刑的
- What? That has nothing to do with us. - I know. I was just saying...
- 怎么了? 那跟我们毫无关系 - 我知道 我只是说
We're doctors. Not judges, not jurors.
我们是医生 不是法官 不是陪审团
Still got the magic touch, huh?
宝刀未老啊?
- What's cracking, D? How ya been? - I'm good, how 'bout you?
- 还好吗 D?你怎么样? - 很好 你呢
Can't complain, man.
没什么好抱怨的
- Kids? - Killin' it. Maggie's getting all A's, and Jack's playing football, starting quarterback.
- 孩子们? - 棒极了
- Just like his old man. - Yeah. Except better, and smarter.
- 跟他老爸一样 - 是啊 只不过更出色 更聪明
Hey, thanks for meeting with me on such short notice.
嘿 多谢你临时赶来见我
- I appreciate it. - Tell me what you need.
- 我很感谢 - 告诉我你有什么事儿
I'm working an undercover case, I need to put some pressure on a suspect.
我在办一个秘密情报的案子 需要给疑犯施加压力
Shake him down. I need an arrest, nothing major, doesn't even have to stick.
吓唬吓唬他 需要逮捕他 不用什么大罪 不合理都没事儿
Guy's name is Jack Cahill.
那家伙叫Jack Cahill
You in the bathroom?
你在卫生间?
What the hell are you doing?
你做什么?
Told you before, I need to know where you are at all times.
之前告诉过你 我需要随时知道你在哪儿
What you did today, going to the cops.
你今天的所作所为 去找警察
You're lucky Duncan didn't tell me to put you down.
Duncan没让我弄死你 算你走运
You are definitely gonna be the hottest First Lady in recent history.
你绝对会是近代史上最性感的第一夫人
- What about Jackie Kennedy? - Not even close.
- 那Jackie Kennedy呢 - 差远了
So, how did your meeting go with the Vice President?
你和副总统的谈话谈得如何?
Very well.
很顺利
He said he would be lucky as hell to have someone like you on his circuit.
他说他很幸运有你这样的同僚
- Love you. - Mmm-hmm?
爱你
One more thing,
还有件事 今天去了司法部长的办公室 拍了他的马屁
He and Vice President Grant are good friends.
他和Grant副总统是好朋友
I will make up a reason to pay him a visit this afternoon.
我今天下午会找个借口去拜访他的
Good.
很好
Just keep it quiet.
保持低调
You don't want anyone to know that you're lobbying for this.
你不会希望有任何人知道你赞成这件事
Are you Dr. Sanders?
你是Sanders医生?
Yes.
是
That was my father, the man you saved.
你救的那个人 是我父亲
Oh, well, he's gonna pull through.
他会没事的
I know my father has a lot of problems, um,
我知道我父亲有很多问题
I don't know if he killed that police man or what, but either way,
我不知道他有没有杀那个警察 但不管怎样
he's still a person, and he's still my father, so,
他还是一个人 也是我的父亲 所以...
thank you for taking care of him.
谢谢你救了他
Scotch, please.
威士忌 谢谢
You look familiar. You work for the Bureau?
你很眼熟 是在局里工作的吗
I used to, 20 years ago.
曾经是 20年前
- Where are you now? - Secret Service.
- 现在呢 - 特勤处
Duncan Carlisle, FBI.
Duncan Carlisle FBI
- Jack Cahill, nice to meet you. - You too.
- Jack Cahill 很高兴认识你 - 我也是
What division are you with?
你在哪个部门
- Crisis negotiation. - Good for you.
- 危机谈判 - 不错啊
Has its moments.
是辉煌过
You seen Sandrine?
你见到Sandrine了吗?
She came back with me a few hours ago. She's around here somewhere. Why?
她几小时前跟我一起回来的 应该就在这儿 怎么了
Just wondering.
就是问问
Why don't you just focus on babysitting this one?
你干嘛不专心照顾这个呢?
Don't got anywhere, Brian. I'll be right back.
哪儿也不要去 Brian 我马上回来
Leave a message.
请留言
Hey, Sandrine, it's me.
嘿 Sandrine 是我
Just checkin' in. Call me when you can.
就是问候一下 有空打给我
Come on, come on.
接电话啊 接电话
- Hello? - Hi, is this Nina?
- 喂? - 嗨 是Nina吗?
Yes, who is this?
是 你是谁?
- My name is Brian Sanders. - Um, do I know you?
- 我是Brian Sanders - 我认识你吗
No.
不认识
I'm confused, why are you calling?
我不明白 你为什么打来?
- What's this about? - I know your husband, Duncan.
- 有什么事 - 我认识你丈夫 Duncan
I'm calling, because...
我打来是因为...他绑架了我的家人
Look, I know this sounds impossible,
我知道这听上去不可思议
but, on the lives of my two kids, it is true, every word.
但是以我两个孩子的性命发誓 这是真的 千真万确
I don't believe you. Is this some sort of sick joke?
我不相信你 这是什么变态玩笑吗
Look, my wife came to visit you the other day.
听我说 我妻子几天前去看过你
You thought she was an alternative doctor?
你以为她是个怪医生?
- That was your wife? - Yeah. Her name is Ellen Sanders.
- 那是你妻子? - 对 她叫Ellen Sanders
She's operating on the President in three days. Look it up online if you have to.
三天后她要给总统动手术 不信你可以上网查
So, you're telling me that the President is...
那你是要告诉我 总统是...
Your biological father, yeah.
你的生父 没错
And my husband,
而我丈夫
- is holding your family hostage? - Yes! For the past two weeks.
- 绑架了你们全家? - 是的 已经两星期了
Your husband has lost his mind. Innocent people are dying.
你丈夫疯了 无辜的人危在旦夕
You have to stop him! Now!
你必须阻止他 马上!
What's making me crazy is the idea of losing you.
一想到要失去你 我就要发疯
- Some things are just beyond our control. - There are other ways.
- 有些事情超出了我们的控制范围 - 还有其他办法的
Other choices we can make.
我们可以做其他选择
- Is it legal? - It's a chance.
- 合法吗 - 是个机会
Our only chance.
我们唯一的机会
I know you're sick, but I don't care!
我知道你病了 但我不在乎
If my family dies, it's on you! Not your father, not your husband,
如果我家人死了 都算在你头上 不是你父亲 不是你丈夫
you!
是你
The hardest part about having a simple life, is being a spectator.
过简单生活最难的地方 就是当一个旁观者
You wanna help, do something, but...
你想帮忙 就做点什么 但是...
I can relate. My wife's in the hospital too.
我感同身受 我妻子也在医院里
She was in a car accident a few years ago.
几年前她出了车祸
- She suffered some brain trauma. - I'm sorry to hear that.
- 脑部受损 - 我很遗憾
You're right, though, about how tough it is.
不过你说得没错 是很难
Whether you like it or not, you, uh, you're helpless.
不管你喜欢与否 你都很无助
You just have to sit around and hope.
你只能坐在一旁 满怀希望
Easier said than done.
说起来容易做起来难
To getting through it.
要经历这个过程
Sorry, could you get that bartender's attention for me?
抱歉 你能帮我叫那个酒保吗
- No problem. Phil? - Yeah.
- 没问题 Phil? - 是
It's the same.
再来一杯
- Okay if I squeeze in here? - Be my guest.
- 我可以过来挤一下吗 - 请便
I'm Nicole.
我是Nicole
- Jack. - Jack.
- Jack
I always liked that name. Never met a Jack who wasn't a decent guy.
我一向很喜欢这个名字 遇到过Jack都是好男人
Hello, Vanessa.
你好 Vanessa
Lyn. Hello!
Lyn 你好啊
- Always a pleasure. - How are you holdin' up?
- 很荣幸 - 你还好吗
I'm okay.
挺好的
- But... - What, what is it?
- 不过... - 什么 怎么了?
Come here.
过来
I'm a little concerned about Colonel Blair.
我有点担心Blair上校
It's probably nothing, but I heard he was meeting today with the Attorney General.
应该没事 不过我听说 他今天要和司法部长见面
Well, I'm sure he had a reason.
我相信他是有原因的
You would think so, but when I spoke to him, he...
想是这么想 但我跟他聊天的时候 他
He lied.
他撒了谎 他说他根本没离开过办公室
You don't think the Colonel's getting nervous and looking to cut a deal?
你说上校不会是紧张了 想要妥协吧
Well, either it's a coincidence or it's a problem,
要么是巧合 要么就是出问题了
and as I don't believe in the former, I'm gonna presume that it's the latter.
因为我不相信是前者 我只能假设是后者
So, let me make a few calls.
让我打几个电话
See what's going on.
打听一下情况
We split up about a year ago.
我们一年前分开的 他人不错 就是有点自私
All he talked about was his job and his problems, I just...
他只想着他的工作和烦恼 我...
- I felt like I was all alone. - Well, you have to talk,
- 我觉得自己很孤单 - 你们得聊天
laugh, connect. I mean, that's the whole point of being with someone, right?
要笑 沟通 这不就是两个人在一起的意义吗 对吗
Exactly!
没错
I'm gonna get out of here. Good to meet you.
我得走了 很高兴见到你
You too.
我也是
Well, are you sure this guy's hooking up tonight?
- 你确定这家伙今晚会上钩? - 他应该随时都会出来
Who is he?
他是谁
Off-duty Secret Service agent.
下班的特勤处特工
- It's complicated. - Okay, fine.
- 一句话说不清楚 - 好吧 行
Forget I asked.
就当我没问
So,
那...
how's Nina doing? Any better?
Nina怎么样? 好点了吗
- I think she's gonna pull through. - Really?
- 我想她会没事的 - 真的吗?
I'm thrilled. I, you know...
我很高兴 我...
You know, to tell you the truth, uh, I was afraid to ask.
说实话 我都不敢问
- I'm happy for you. - Thanks.
- 我真为你开心 - 谢谢
There he is.
他来了
Thanks for giving me a ride.
多谢你送我
No problem, it's on my way. I live over on Capitol Hill.
小意思 反正顺路 我就住在国会山
Thank you.
谢谢
Um, I'm sorry, but I'm married. I should've said something earlier.
抱歉 但我结婚了 我应该早点说的
Well, I won't tell if you don't.
你不说我都看不出来
I'm flattered but, uh, I can't. It's a long story.
我很荣幸 但是...我不可以 说来话长了
- You're not attracted to me? - No! You're beautiful, trust me. Just...
- 你对我没兴趣? - 不是 你很美 相信我 但是...
I love my wife.
我爱我的妻子
Well, that's really sweet.
真有爱
I could still give you a ride home, there's no rule against that.
我可以送你回家 这不违反规定
- Please step out of the vehicle. - What for?
- 请下车 - 为什么
Sir, please step out of the vehicle. DC Police.
先生 请下车 华盛顿警察
- We were just talking, Officer. - Just keep your mouth shut.
- 我们只是聊天 长官 - 闭上嘴
You're facing solicitation charges, so just sit tight...
你将面临教唆指控 所以老实坐着
Whoa, whoa. Solicitation? Look, you got things mixed up, fella.
喔喔 教唆? 你误会了 兄弟
- He was just gonna give me a ride... - I'm not gonna ask you again.
- 他只是顺路送我 - 我不会说第二次的
Get out of the vehicle now!
- 马上下车! - 别担心 我来搞定
Listen, you don't have to raise your voice, okay?
你不用提高音量 好吗
Look, just let me explain, all right?
听我解释 好吗
- You don't have to explain anything. - You're under arrest.
你什么都不用解释 你被捕了
- Look, tough guy. I'm just gonna show... - Whoa. Don't touch anything.
- 听着 硬汉 我要... - 什么都不要碰
- I'm just gonna show you... - Keep your hand away from the gun.
- 我要出示... - 手离枪远一点
Amelia just called. You don't have her phone, do you?
Amelia 刚来了电话 她的电话不在你这儿吧
Yeah. I stole it.
在 我偷了
Why?
为什么?
Because, Dad said he needed a phone that couldn't be traced.
因为爸爸说他需要一部查不到的手机
I think he has a plan to get us out of this.
- 我想他有办法让我们逃出去 - 办法?
- I thought Mom told us to cooperate? - She did, but
- 妈妈不是让我们合作吗 - 是 但是...
I don't know what's going on with them. I think...
我也不知道他们是怎么了 我想...
How was work?
工作怎么样
I had a patient with a very complicated surgery.
遇到一个手术很复杂的病人
Did he die?
他死了吗
No.
没有
So, what about us? Do you and Dad have a plan, or?
那我们呢 你和爸爸有什么计划吗 还是?
We're gonna make sure you're safe.
我们要确保你们的安全
Does that mean you've decided to kill the President?
那是说你准备杀总统了?
I heard what happened.
我听说了发生的事
Little more drama than I was expecting, but a win is a win.
比我想的还要混乱 不过赢了就是赢了
An honest cop got shot. That's not a win.
一名好警察中了枪 这不算赢
I apologize,
我道歉
but we accomplished what we set out to do, discredit Cahill.
但我们完成了任务 让Cahill可疑
There's no way he stays on the President's detail after this.
这之后他不会留在总统的特遣队里了
Dead cop, a career hooker in his front seat.
死了一个警察 前座坐了一个职业妓女
So, despite the loss of your colleague...
所以 除了你们的同僚牺牲外...
Friend. My friend.
朋友 是我的朋友
Despite the loss of your friend, this was an operational victory.
除了你们的朋友牺牲外 这次行动是成功的
We're back on track. Logan will be in charge of the detail.
一切恢复正常 Logan会负责保镖管理
We're in this together. You and me.
我们是一条船上的 你和我
One more thing,
还有件事
why do you have two of your people following a federal prosecutor named Steve Patterson?
你为什么派两个人 去跟踪联邦检察官Steve Patterson?
How did you know that?
你怎么知道的?
You forget? I'm with the NSA.
你忘了吗 我是NSA的
Steve Patterson is part of an ongoing FBI investigation,
Steve Patterson参与了FBI的调查
we think he might be playing ball with a drug cartel.
我们认为他或许与贩毒集团合作
Like you, I'm working two jobs right now.
和你一样 我现在打两份工
So, I had to outsource my surveillance work to a few of my team members.
所以我不得不把监视工作外包给手下的人
Good.
很好
I thought you were getting cold feet.
我还以为你怕了
My feet are just fine.
我没问题
Archer?
Archer?
Sandrine took the bait. She's working for the other side.
Sandrine上钩了 她是另一边的人
A hero is strong.
英雄是很坚强的
A hero does things nobody else is brave enough to do.
英雄会做其他人没有勇气做的事
A hero is a good person, who wants to make sure that people are safe and don't die.
英雄是个好人 想要保证他人的安危和性命
That's why my dad is a hero.
所以我爸爸是个英雄
Thank you, honey.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thank you.
谢谢
Just checked my voicemail, Nina called, several times.
我刚查了语音信箱 Nina打来好几次
She's been trying to reach you.
她一直在找你
I told her everything.
我都告诉她了
She's the only one
她是唯一一个
that can stop this madness.
可以阻止这一切疯狂的人
No, she's not.
不 她不是
I can.
是我
I was wrong.
我错了
I mean, I'm a doctor. What was I thinking?
我是个医生 我在想什么啊
I need to tell him I won't do it.
我要告诉他我不会那么做
I am so sorry, Brian.
我很抱歉  Brian
You were right.
你说得对
I just,
我只是...
lost myself.
一时失控
I love you.
我爱你
What's wrong? Are you okay?
怎么了 你还好吗
I talked to Brian Sanders.
我跟Brian Sanders谈过
He told me what's going on, what you've done to his family,
他跟我说了 说你对他家人所做的一切
what you're planning.
你的计划
Is it true?
是真的吗
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入